

IONUT HUSOSCHI

WEB DEVELOPER

About Me

I am a passionate WebDeveloper, ambitious, a person who always wants to learn new things and to deliver high-quality software solutions.

- +40747241177
- ionuthusoschi@gmail.com
- **O** Github Account
- in Linkedin lonut Husoschi
- Website Portfolio

Language

English - fluent

Skills



HTML - 4 years CSS - 4 years

Tailwind - 4 years

Bootstrap - 4 years

Javascript - 4 years

jQuery - 3 years

React Libraries- 2 years

Typescript - 2 years

Next.js - 1 year

REST API - 3 years

Node.js - 1 year

MySQL - 1 year

NoSQL - 1 year

CMS (WP,Strapi) - 1 year

Git, Bitbucket - 4 years basic CI/CD - 1 year

NGINX - 1 year

NoSQL - 1 year

Experience

Virtual Ink

Iasi Romania (Full time)

2020 - present

Build responsive, accessible and dynamic web pages. Integrate REST API's, create reusable components, adding new features, maintain all websites and workflow.

WebRender

CEO (side projects)

2022 - 2024

Ecommerce, blogs, news papers and personal projects with Next.js and Headless CMS (Wordpress, Strapi, Sanity), I create REST API's with Node.js.

Upwork

Freelance

2021 - 2024

Maintain websites, accomplish small tasks, full websites with multipe technologies (Wordpress, React, Next) and help configure webservers.

Education

Universitatea Tehnică "Gheorghe Asachi" din Iași Civil Enginnering 2008-2012

Colegiul National "A.T.Laurian"

Mathematics and Computer Science 2004-2008

Courses

Udemy School

SoloLearn